A handwritten, fun and happy modern calligraphy script font with carefully crafted, clean vectors. You can create beautiful hand-made typography with its bouncy, organic flow. Italian Breakfast is perfect for all your creative projects wether it be 

* indie logos, 
* printed quotes, 
* invitations, 
* greeting cards,
* Instagram posts, 
* products, packaging, 
* blog headers etc.

Happy creating and have fun!

Fonts are provided in TTF & OTF formats. I recommend installing the TTF files, and the OTF only if necessary. There is no difference between these two unless for printing ttf is better.



You may not

- sell these fonts or claim them as your own.

- edit or rename these fonts.

- redistribute these fonts.


http://rbfonts.com
rbfonts@yahoo.com
